Contact

kylebasilio@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kylebasilio (LinkedIn)

Kyle Basilio

BSN '20 Graduate at West Coast University

United States

Summary

A BSN graduate with the drive to pursue a career in flight nursing. Interested in the ICU/ER and also mental health care, offering previous direct patient care experience of 1 year as an LVN, to help impact the lives of those in need.

Experience

Kindred Healthcare
Licensed Practical Nurse
March 2018 - March 2019 (1 year 1 month)
Baldwin Park, California, United States

Tillys
Parttime Sales Associate
December 2017 - June 2018 (7 months)

Glendora, California, United States

COVINA REHABILITATION CENTER Licensed Practical Nurse

August 2017 - December 2017 (5 months)

The Walt Disney Company 2 years 1 month

Covina, California, United States

Parade Performer March 2014 - March 2016 (2 years 1 month) Anaheim, California, United States

Characters

November 2014 - February 2015 (4 months)

Anaheim, California, United States

abercrombie kids
Parttime Sales Associate

June 2013 - June 2014 (1 year 1 month)

Arcadia, California, United States

Education

West Coast University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2018 - 2020)

Premiere Career College

Licensed Practical/Vocational Nurse Training · (2015 - 2016)